{
  "students": [
    {
      "id": "1402037",
      "name": "Naol Meseret",
      "department": "software enginering",
      "username": "naolm",
      "password": "123456",
      "year": 4,
      "courses": [
        {
          "coursecode": 1,
          "coursename": "mats",
          "coursescore": 87
        },
        {
          "coursecode": 2,
          "coursename": "physics",
          "coursescore": 100
        },
        {
          "coursecode": 3,
          "coursename": "history",
          "coursescore": 30
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "87664",
      "name": "fuad seid",
      "username": "fuad34",
      "password": "fuad34",
      "department": "software enginering",
      "year": "2",
      "courses": [
        {
          "coursecode": "65",
          "coursename": "chemistry",
          "coursescore": "97"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "123456",
      "name": "abedla ",
      "username": "abdela45",
      "password": "abdela34",
      "department": "software enginering",
      "year": "1",
      "courses": [
        {
          "coursecode": "457",
          "coursename": "compiler design",
          "coursescore": 0
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "123566",
      "name": "firaol",
      "username": "naol528",
      "password": "Naol@1234",
      "department": "software enginering",
      "year": "2",
      "courses": [
        {
          "coursecode": "54666",
          "coursename": "mars",
          "coursescore": 0
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "123456",
      "name": "solomon mandefro ",
      "username": "sol",
      "password": "sol1234",
      "department": "information tecnology",
      "year": "4",
      "courses": [
        {
          "coursecode": "123456",
          "coursename": "mats",
          "coursescore": 0
        },
        {
          "coursecode": "147654",
          "coursename": "compiler",
          "coursescore": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "127888",
      "name": "abdela nesredin",
      "username": "abdela",
      "password": "12345678",
      "department": "software enginering",
      "year": "4",
      "courses": [
        {
          "coursecode": "987878",
          "coursename": "mats",
          "coursescore": 0
        },
        {
          "coursecode": "147654",
          "coursename": "english",
          "coursescore": null
        },
        {
          "coursecode": "123456",
          "coursename": "compiler",
          "coursescore": null
        },
        {
          "coursecode": "123456",
          "coursename": "java",
          "coursescore": null
        },
        {
          "coursecode": "147654",
          "coursename": "MAD",
          "coursescore": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "123478",
      "name": "Habtamu ",
      "username": "habtamu34",
      "password": "12345678",
      "department": "Kebede",
      "year": "3",
      "courses": [
        {
          "coursecode": "123456",
          "coursename": "artefical intelegence",
          "coursescore": 0
        },
        {
          "coursecode": "8898999",
          "coursename": "matimatics",
          "coursescore": null
        },
        {
          "coursecode": "8898999",
          "coursename": "compile design",
          "coursescore": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "870896",
      "name": "meron getnet",
      "username": "meron@1234",
      "password": "meron1234",
      "department": "software enginering",
      "year": "4",
      "courses": [
        {
          "coursecode": "8898999",
          "coursename": "compiler",
          "coursescore": 0
        },
        {
          "coursecode": "987878",
          "coursename": "software security",
          "coursescore": null
        },
        {
          "coursecode": "987878",
          "coursename": "software testing",
          "coursescore": null
        },
        {
          "coursecode": "987878",
          "coursename": "software enginering",
          "coursescore": null
        },
        {
          "coursecode": "987878",
          "coursename": "advanced",
          "coursescore": null
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "dfa2",
      "subject": "computer programing",
      "coursecode": "123456",
      "finishtime": "10:00",
      "starttime": "00:00",
      "autecode": "appdev",
      "questionss": [
        {
          "question": "what is the the output of this code ?",
          "option": [
            "baltazar",
            "mia khalifa",
            "mnm",
            "mnmn"
          ],
          "answer": "1"
        }
      ],
      "date": "2024-12-25"
    },
    {
      "id": "122a",
      "subject": "mats",
      "coursecode": "8898999",
      "finishtime": "00:55",
      "starttime": "03:55",
      "date": "2024-12-26",
      "autecode": "appdev",
      "questionss": [
        {
          "question": "who is the legend in 21 centurey?",
          "option": [
            "baltazar",
            "mia khalifa",
            "jhony sins",
            "p dididy"
          ],
          "answer": "3"
        },
        {
          "question": "who is the legend in 21 centurey?",
          "option": [
            "baltazar",
            "mia khalifa",
            "jhony sins",
            "p dididy"
          ],
          "answer": "2"
        },
        {
          "question": "who is the legend in 21 centurey?",
          "option": [
            "baltazar",
            "mia khalifa",
            "jhony sins",
            "p dididy"
          ],
          "answer": "4"
        },
        {
          "question": "who is the legend in 21 centurey?",
          "option": [
            "baltazar",
            "mia khalifa",
            "jhony sins",
            "p dididy"
          ],
          "answer": "1"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "165c",
      "subject": "web programing",
      "coursecode": "987878",
      "finishtime": "00:16",
      "starttime": "03:16",
      "date": "2024-12-25",
      "autecode": "appdev",
      "questionss": [
        {
          "question": "who is the legend in 21 centurey?",
          "option": [
            "nbambd",
            "manmdan",
            "manmdna",
            ",ammda"
          ],
          "answer": "1"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "5f31",
      "subject": "matimatics",
      "coursecode": "45678",
      "finishtime": "09:45",
      "starttime": "01:45",
      "date": "2024-12-25",
      "autecode": "appdev",
      "questionss": [
        {
          "question": "what is the the out putof this code ?",
          "option": [
            "amna",
            "mnm",
            "manmdna",
            "mand"
          ],
          "answer": "1"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "cdbd",
      "subject": "app development ",
      "coursecode": "453718",
      "finishtime": "18:22",
      "starttime": "20:23",
      "date": "2024-12-25",
      "autecode": "appdev",
      "questionss": [
        {
          "question": "who is the legend in 21 centurey?",
          "option": [
            "baltazar",
            "mia khalifa",
            "jhony sins",
            "p dididy"
          ],
          "answer": "1"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "7a02",
      "subject": "chemistry",
      "coursecode": "1234598",
      "finishtime": "04:17",
      "starttime": "2:18",
      "date": "2024-12-27",
      "autecode": "chem",
      "questionss": [
        {
          "question": "who is the legend in 21 centurey?",
          "option": [
            "baltazar",
            "mia khalifa",
            "jhony sins",
            "p dididy"
          ],
          "answer": "1"
        },
        {
          "question": "who is the legend in 21 centurey?",
          "option": [
            "baltazar",
            "manmdan",
            "manam",
            "mananmna"
          ],
          "answer": "2"
        },
        {
          "question": "who is the best from the porn stars ?",
          "option": [
            "bambi",
            "mia khalifa",
            "jhony sins",
            "dibora"
          ],
          "answer": "3"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "5c77",
      "subject": "computer programing",
      "coursecode": "765477",
      "finishtime": "00:21",
      "starttime": "03:21",
      "date": "2024-12-28",
      "autecode": "fuck",
      "questionss": [
        {
          "question": "what is the output of console.log(\"jhony sins\")",
          "option": [
            "best pornstar",
            "big dick",
            "aim at the pussy",
            "fucker"
          ],
          "answer": "1"
        },
        {
          "question": "what is the output of console.log(\"bambi\")",
          "option": [
            "shele ",
            "bdatam",
            "fengari",
            "teletlach"
          ],
          "answer": "1"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "6b31",
      "subject": "compiler design",
      "coursecode": "123456",
      "finishtime": "18:54",
      "starttime": "13:54",
      "date": "2024-12-28",
      "autecode": "compiler",
      "questionss": [
        {
          "question": "what are the phases of compiler?",
          "option": [
            "4",
            "3",
            "8",
            "7"
          ],
          "answer": "1"
        },
        {
          "question": "what is the difference between compiler and interpreter",
          "option": [
            "there are 4 differences",
            "how can you develop the software without knowing compiler and interpreter ",
            "please read be carefull about you read from option b",
            "helllo you are the gratest man in the history "
          ],
          "answer": "4"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "74eb",
      "subject": "man",
      "coursecode": "123456",
      "finishtime": "20:01",
      "starttime": "12:59",
      "date": "2024-12-27",
      "autecode": "appdev",
      "questionss": [
        {
          "question": "who is the legend in 21 centurey?",
          "option": [
            "abjabdjbsahj",
            "manmd,",
            "amnd",
            ",ammda"
          ],
          "answer": "nmmn"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}